(THE YARNS)
This is the new victim I'm going to kill.
I have ten hours for you.
If you're even a second late, she's dead.
Five.
Four
Who has these genes?
Come out and kill them all.
Come out quickly, everyone, come out now.
Order all units to thoroughly
patrol every school in Bangkok.
Especially Arunpanya School
Sergeant Sookwan is at Arunpanya School.
Hello, where are you?
- Where are you, Rapee?
- Teachers' room
Rapee, hurry up and go to
the security guard booth right now.
- What's up, honey?
- Sookwan went back to school for some reason.
- Go now.
- Okay, okay.
Hello, what are you here to contact me about?
Has Rapeephan come down yet?
He's in the teacher's lounge.
- Sergeant.
- Hey, Sergeant Moo.
The item is still there.
Sergeant, please call Rapee again.
Hey, stop!
I told you to stop.
Rapee
Sir,
-This time there are two pieces?
- Yes
So, in conclusion,
this incident is a serial murder, right?
This is a restricted area. Please leave.
Please answer me first, Inspector.
Are you a murderer? Am I the real one?
Lieutenant,
Sir,
- Please...
- The one who was caught was a scapegoat, right?
People must know this.
You, you are not allowed to take pictures.
Let go of me, sir.
6th corpse released. You have to tell the truth.
How long are you going to keep hiding it from the public?
- The staff is working.
- Inspector
People are not safe because of you.
- Sir.
- Get out, please.
Everyone, can you see now that the police are hiding things from the people?
Now, you won't tell me the truth.
Inspector, you're silent...
The common people
Aren't our eyes black or something?
This reporter is a moron.
Don't you know?
That you went to report the news in a prohibited place.
It spoils the case.
An
What are the autopsy results for Rapi?
Brother Rapee
Rapee died from gas inhalation.
Too much helium
Used in balloons
Although helium is an inert, non-flammable gas,
But if you inhale too much, your body will absorb it.
It can also cause unconsciousness and death.
That's strange.
How did the culprit carry
such a large gas tank into the school?
Without anyone seeing
Um, two days ago there was a school festival at school.
Balloons were distributed to students.
I think it was around that time.
Have you questioned those people yet?
Yes
Received a report that a gas tank
went missing after work.
And check the fingerprints on the tank.
Every fingerprint owner has witnesses who can identify their whereabouts at the time of the incident.
Oh, damn!
How is it going?
Okay, send it to Nawin immediately.
The CCTV camera in front of the school
captured the image of a car.
A few minutes after the incident
The picture is here, Inspector.
Zoom in
- Ms. Sookwan
What are you doing at school so late at night, Sookwan?
Why?
I just left school at the same time that Raphipan died.
I became a murderer
Wow, the police have such an easy job.
Sookwan knows the exact time
of Khun Rapeephan's death.
The news comes out like crazy,
without having to search for anything.
It's all over my feed.
What about this necklace?
Have you ever seen it?
Where did you get that?
It looks like you want it.
- It's my necklace. I dropped it.
- Where?
Well, where did you find it?
The letter S on the necklace
probably stands for your name, Sookwan.
And what does it say that I killed Teacher Rapeephan?
This necklace cannot tell you that you are the culprit who killed Teacher Rapeephan.
But it can confirm that you
Go eavesdrop on Teacher Rapeephan's confession that he wants to expel Sky from school.
- So what?
- You were angry.
I admit that I was angry.
So you think I'm resentful.
So I killed Raphipan. Oh!
Have I become another scapegoat?
The first two
are the person who used to bully Sky.
This person is the one who got Sky kicked out of school.
Is this enough for the motivation?
Are you investigating me and Sky?
You look relieved.
The camera doesn't show who the other person you picked up is.
Can you tell me?
Who did you park your car to pick up?
Will you catch me?
If you don't
I'll go back
Please allow me to interview you.
The murderer
Sergeant!
- Be mindful, Sergeant. Be mindful.
- Are you a police officer?
Would you be crazy if I was a murderer?
Would I let my child decode
the killer and get my child arrested?
My child almost died because of you guys.
As a police officer, use your brains a bit.
Don't just be so crazy. Are you a mad dog?
And who knows about the code woven into the yarn you left on the corpse?
Besides you and your daughter.
It's obvious that you're a psychopathic killer.
Wait a minute, is the code on the yarn real?
Didn't you say that this was a story that the police lieutenant created to anger the criminal?
Isn't the person who can decode this a police officer?
A kidnapped girl was a decoder.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can't answer that right now.
Sergeant,
Take Sookwan to the car.
Sergeant, please be mindful.
- Sergeant, please be mindful, Sergeant.
- The wool killer
Inspector, if you let him go,
he'll have to kill other victims.
Sergeant, I commanded a stop.
I commanded the sergeant to stop.
- Murderer...
- What the hell is going on?
Is it embarrassing?
The murderer was never caught.
And then he assaulted the suspect.
What about the evidence?
So weak that you can't catch anything.
It's my fault.
No, it's not.
It's me who's wrong.
As the head of the forensic team, I still haven't found any evidence that leads to any clues.
Then I am wrong.
The evidence cannot be used to identify the culprit
- I also...
- Okay, okay, that's enough.
No need to compete to show off.
What you guys are doing here means I
am also wrong as your boss.
- No, it's not.
- No, sir.
Have you ordered Sergeant Moo to be suspended yet?
All right, sir.
oh
Why are you standing? Just sit down. What are you waiting for? Are you waiting to get a star?
- Yes
- All useless.
Inspector
Let me be honest.
In your eyes,
Is Sookwan a murderer?
Hey, stop!
Stopper
At last
I went back to the scene of the incident again.
Let's try walking from the auditorium to the parking lot.
It takes about ten minutes.
From CCTV footage
We will see that Sookwan's car
left the school in three minutes.
After I saw the back of the murderer
So I tried running.
It still took me more than three minutes.
So I think it's impossible for Sookwan
to do it in less than three minutes.
Let's say you're sure that Sookwan isn't the murderer.
Umm
I'm not sure.
It is possible that there are more than just one murderer.
Sookwan may not be the killer, but she is the driver who is picking up someone at the meeting point.
Because when I questioned Sookwan, she looked suspicious about this point.
The murderer has now killed 6 people.
We have no evidence at all.
DNA
Bloodstains, nothing at all
We have a puzzle made from yarn.
How long are you going to chase this yarn mystery?
How many people do you have to wait for to die?
But this time we can get this close to the murderer.
It's because of this yarn.
I believe that if he continues to decode it,
We will be able to narrow everything down and finally catch the murderer, sir.
Are you referring to the girl who decoded the code?
yes
Go get her.
- You mean, bring her here?
- Well, why is there a problem here?
- Sky is an autistic child.
- Oh, so what?
Then bring her here.
I would like to see this kid
How she solves the riddle with my own eyes
I won't let you go.
What is this? You're calling me a serial killer.
And then you come and ask for help from my daughter.
Seriously, police, if I were a murderer,
Would I let my daughter help the people who were going to catch her mother? Huh?
I'm really sorry.
I have to do my duty.
Therefore, it is necessary to interrogate Sookwan.
What are you talking about,
Sergeant Pig and Sergeant Dog?
Who came and shouted and strangled me,
calling me a murderer?
Let me lose face
This is all over my feed, look, look.
Everyone called me a murderer,
so I couldn't open my shop.
Has any police officer ever come out and apologized and said that I am not a murderer?
And then you come and ask for help from my daughter.
Go back.
Go.
Sookwan.
I sincerely apologize.
No need. Go back.
Sky
Mom, please take this candy to make you smile first.
Please calm down, Mom.
This is yours, police officer.
Sky
Go, go back now.
What
What help do you need from the police?
- Go back. You can go back now.
- Mom, can you please stop talking for now?
Please eat this candy and calm down first.
- Sky
- What help do you need from me, police?
I want Sky.
- help...
- No one can help you. Go back.
Sky, of course.
Sky can help us.
Oh, stop messing with my child.
Mom, you taught me that if Sky helps others,
our society will improve.
If we help each other, society will improve.
- Sky
- Sky, someone just sent me two new codes.
Code...Which two pieces?
- Sky
- I'm in my office. Sky has to go there to decode.
I won't let her go.
Ms. Sookwan, please, I beg you.
Sky is the only one who can help us.
Oh, stop messing with my kid.
Mom, Sky is going to your police office.
Sky
Sky will go because Sky doesn't want anyone to criticize
That my mother is a murderer
Mom is not a murderer.
Policeman, Sky will go to your office.
Then mom will go with you.
This is a state secret.
And Sky is the only one who is allowed.
What's your problem? Then I won't let her go.
Sky
Mom,
Sky can handle this myself.
This is the person who was taken hostage last time.
Does it look strange?
Will this really help?
Look at her expression.
She seems to be completely stupid.
Who said that? She wasn't stupid. She's called a special child.
It's okay, Sky.
Come with me, don't be afraid.
This one really and this one must have a camera.
Where did the image go?
It's broken, sir.
I'll check for you.
Just a moment, please.
Sky
Wait, Sky will sit over there.
This is the code that I need you to help decode.
Sky
Are you okay?
Don't let anything happen to you here. You can't do it.
Sky, Sky, listen to me.
Sky, calm down first.
Don't be afraid
I'm with Sky here.
Oh, stop!
Stop pressing the pen, Sky is annoyed.
Lan, I think Sky might not be used to this many people.
Everyone, should we go outside?
Just leave this room with Sky and Lan.
I want to see this kid decode it.
Sir, then how about this?
Wait, let me stay here and decode it just the two of us.
But everyone can see and hear it.
how
Sky... I'm ready.
QR code.
This bar is a QR code.
QR code, Sky?
So what should I do next, Sky?
Please wait a moment.
Oh my gosh, what is this?
- Lieutenant, do something.
- Yes
Should we start unpacking?
Sky
finished
Now that we're done, what do we do next, Sky?
Got it. It's so easy.
- What is it, Inspector?
- A book.
I think we should get this book.
See you, Sky.
Medical science and the barriers to humanity
- Nawin
- Yes
- Go get this book right away.
- Yes, sir.
And what about the second one, Sky?
I tried looking at it, but it's neither Morse code nor Braille.
It just looks like an ordinary number.
Yes, it's just a number.
The first row is 11/20.
But if it's like this, it won't be connected to the puzzle from the previous yarn, Sky.
But every time the puzzles in the yarn are connected.
But this time it's not.
Sky remembers, right? It's a number that tells the order in which each victim was killed.
1/10 2/10 3/10 4/10 5/10
This time it should be 6/10.
But it's not.
Or is it 6/10?
Is it hidden in here?
No, no, no.
6/10 It's in
Where is it in this yarn?
Or that
6/10 What number is it hiding in, Sky?
Yes, the police are very good. 11/20
If you convert it to a quinary number, you get exactly 6/10.
Is that base five, Sky?
Yes, we need to get all the numbers in this yarn.
Let's make it a quinary number.
Please help me, Sky.
Sure, it's easy. Sky likes it.
This is the book you ordered.
Medical science and the barriers to humanity
The book that goes against
Killer Gene Law
It's all related here, isn't it?
Sir, Sky has finished decoding.
are 27 rows of numbers in total.
Each row is divided into 3 sets of numbers.
The first set, the middle set,
and the last set are as follows.
There's definitely no mistake.
And what do these numbers mean, Sky?
I don't know.
Lan, can you and Mark help Sky?
Sky
Sky, listen to me. It's like this.
I would like to ask my friends
Can you help Sky decode it?
Whose friend is this?
Sky doesn't have any friends except the police.
These are my friends.
And he also wanted to be friends with Sky.
Sky, can you ask your friends to help you decode?
Because my friends also like to decode like us.
can they?
Sir,
Can I have a book? Maybe I can help you with something.
Sky, please let me see this too.
Do you think it's related in any way?
I have no idea.
What's wrong, Sky?
I can't think of any.
What's in the code?
Sky can't figure it out.
I can't think of it.
Sky, let's do it this way.
If you can't think of anything, that's okay.
I'll take you home.
No way. I won't go back.
Sky has to figure it out. Figure it out
What's in the code?
What is this?
Give the numbers to the book
But the book only talks about human equality.
There is nothing else.
Yes, book cipher.
Or Ottendorf cipher
Book Code
It is a code in which each word or letter in the text is replaced by some code in the text of another book.
Each row of numbers represents one letter.
It may be a vowel or a tone mark.
The first set of numbers is the page number.
The second set of numbers is the line and the last set of numbers is that character.
So the short puzzle is in that book.
Got it.
This book is the key.
The code has 27 rows in total.
This means that 27 characters must be decoded.
That's right
So let's get started. Mark, read the numbers.
- Open the book. I'll take notes myself.
- Sure
- Sky
- First Page 89
- Any pen.
- 89
Line 51
Letter 27
Just a moment.
T. Tao
Next, page 45.
- OKay
- Row number 24
- Okay
- Number 14
14, huh?
R. Ruea
- R. Ruea
- Next page 219
- Okay
- Line 32
Number 9
Vowel E
Next page 151
Vowel A
Triyampawai
Died from swinging
What is your occupation?
So you're a Brahmin?
Is the next victim a Brahmin?
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute.
What is this tri-trumpet riddle clue?
Does it mean Brahmin?
It's the Triyampawai ceremony, sir.
Tripavai is a Hindu religious ritual.
There will be a swing at the swing pole in front of Wat Suthat.
And every year a Brahmin who performs
the ceremony falls to his death.
This eventually led to the ceremony being canceled.
From all the clues
- It matches the puzzle.
- Yeah
Hey, are there still Brahmins these days, Sergeant?
There's not much left, sir.
I have already assigned the team to find the names and keep a close watch on them.
Yeah, good.
Don't let the news get out who the next victim is.
understand
Oh, and where is the kid who decoded the code now?
I'm at home, sir. Our team is keeping watch.
But when I leave here,
I will continue to watch over you myself.
Good
Be extremely careful with your safety. Don't miss out.
Because this child is the only one who might be able to lead us to the murderer.
Yes, sir.
Yes!
And how is Sergeant Moo?
- Rapi, I'm sorry for causing Rapi to die.
- Sergeant.
- Let me go in and see Raphi's face.
Sergeant, listen.
Phi Rapi's body was seized and cannot be entered.
- Let me in.
- I understand, sir.
- Listen first.
Sergeant
sergeant
Police Sergeant
Sir,
I shouldn't have made Rapee wait at school.
Sergeant, Sergeant, listen to me.
The sergeant did nothing wrong.
Everything that Sergeant did was
because he was worried about Phi Rapi.
Phi Rapee knows, Sergeant.
- I have no one left. I have no one left.
- Sergeant.
You have me.
I love you, sir.
I love the sergeant like a real brother.
Sergeant, listen to me carefully
and think about what I mean.
Now, Phi Rapi is in a good place,
but if Sergeant is still like this,
How much does he care about the sergeant?
It's okay, Sergeant.
nevermind
If you can't handle it, come cry to me, Sergeant.
Come on, Sergeant.
Wait a minute, Lan.
Are you really going to stay at home and watch over the mother and daughter all night?
um
yes
Even though people were sent to guard
those who could fall prey
Isn't it a good idea to keep watch over Sookwan?
But Lan said that it probably wasn't Sookwan.
But we already told you that we can't cut anyone off.
Isn't it because of Sky?
Seems like you're very worried about her.
yes
We have to watch Sky.
Because she is the only one who can lead us to the real killer.
It's not like you think.
- You can go back today. I'll take care of it myself.
- Yes
It's about to rain.
Should we call the police into the house?
It's better to let him stay outside.
Mom,
But the police officer is Sky's friend.
He once saved Sky's life.
Sky will let you, the policeman,
Sleep in the car while it's raining.
That's not a good friend.
Sky will call the police into the house.
Sky, stop this right now.
Stop messing with that cop.
Listen to mom.
If Sky has the same symptoms again,
don't leave the room, understand?
If you can't stand it, just call mom.
Or else, just knit some yarn.
So that you can concentrate better.
Don't leave the room, understand?
- But the police
- No but, just sleep.
Or go sleep with me?
Then go to sleep.
sleep
Must die
Must die, must die.
Must die, must die
Must die
Let me go
help
Die again Die again
Died again
What to do?
Die again Die again
Died again
Die again, die again
Sookwan.
Sky
Get out, get out. Don't mess
with Sky's stuff. Get out, get out.
Sky, it's me, Sky.
- Sky, it's me, the police officer.
- Get out. Don't mess with Sky's stuff. Get out.
- Sky, I'm not doing anything, Sky. It's me, Sky.
- Get out!
- Policeman Sky Sky
- Don't mess with Sky's stuff. Get out!
- Get out!
- Inspector
Get out! Don't mess with Sky's stuff! Get out!
How did you get into my daughter's room? Get out!
Get out now!
If you don't go out, I will tell the reporters that you want to do something bad to my daughter.
Go out
No, Sookwan, I just saw the yarn fall down
- So I picked it up for you.
- Go out
I told you to get out.
- Yes
Sky, there's nothing left.
Sky Sky
Um
I'm about to call you now.
7th Corpse
There were 2 bodies.